[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the first brown supermarket grocery bag appear?", "correct_answer": "1871", "incorrect_answers": ["1903", "1915", "1911"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dasht-e Kavir and Kavir-e Lut are deserts located in this Asian country.", "correct_answer": "Iran", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Pakistan", "Iraq"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Biotin deficiency (the lack of vitamin B7) is a rare nutritional disorder that occurs in people from this age group.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Adults", "Elderly people", "Infants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only stable chemical element whose atom can contain no neutrons at all in its nucleus?", "correct_answer": "Hydrogen-1", "incorrect_answers": ["Oxygen-1", "There is no such element.", "Helium-3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Excessive salt consumption can lead to high blood pressure.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What magazine selects The Person of the Year?", "correct_answer": "Time", "incorrect_answers": ["Newsweek", "Sports Illustrated", "Rolling Stones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Biggin Hill in London, that is said to be haunted by ghosts, was what kind of war location in the past?", "correct_answer": "World War II airbase", "incorrect_answers": ["World War I airbase", "Revolutionary War strategy base", "D-Day commandment center"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of the New York City boroughs is Rockefeller Center situated?", "correct_answer": "Manhattan", "incorrect_answers": ["Brooklyn", "Queens", "The Bronx"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1982 courtroom drama movie stars Paul Newman as alcoholic lawyer Frank Galvin.", "correct_answer": "The Verdict", "incorrect_answers": ["The Firm", "The Case", "The Juror"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The TV show Medium revolves around a psychic consultant named Allison Du Bois. True or False: The character is named after a real life psychic consultant called Allison DuBois.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Watchmen, where did Dr. Manhattan go after he became upset during his interview?", "correct_answer": "Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["California", "Bosnia", "Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the rifle-carrying Rojos brother in the movie A Fistful of Dollars?", "correct_answer": "Ramon", "incorrect_answers": ["Sita", "Ricardo", "Estaban"]}]